{
    "results": [
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "Arrested_Development.mp3",
            "category": "TV",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the TV show",
            "correct_answer": "Arrested Development",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Curb Your Enthusiasm",
                "Modern Family",
                "Community"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "Blackadder.mp3",
            "category": "TV",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the TV show",
            "correct_answer": "Blackadder",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Black Books",
                "Upstart Crow",
                "The Vicar of Dibley"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "Breaking_Bad.mp3",
            "category": "TV",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the TV show",
            "correct_answer": "Breaking Bad",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Sons of Anarchy",
                "The Wire",
                "Prison Break"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "Brooklyn_Nine-Nine.mp3",
            "category": "TV",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the TV show",
            "correct_answer": "Brooklyn Nine-Nine",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Parks and Recreation",
                "The Good Place",
                "Superstore"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "Chernobyl.mp3",
            "category": "TV",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the TV show",
            "correct_answer": "Chernobyl",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Watchmen",
                "Titanic",
                "Black Mirror"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "Colombo.mp3",
            "category": "TV",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the TV show",
            "correct_answer": "Colombo",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Quincy",
                "Ironside",
                "Diagnosis Murder"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "Countdown.mp3",
            "category": "TV",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the TV show",
            "correct_answer": "Countdown",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "The Weakest Link",
                "Eggheads",
                "Pointless"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "Dark.mp3",
            "category": "TV",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the TV show",
            "correct_answer": "Dark",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Disappeared",
                "The OA",
                "Mindhunter"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "Dexter.mp3",
            "category": "TV",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the TV show",
            "correct_answer": "Dexter",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Ballers",
                "CSI: Miami",
                "Miami Vice"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "Fawlty_Towers.mp3",
            "category": "TV",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the TV show",
            "correct_answer": "Fawlty Towers",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "The Good Life",
                "One Foot in the Grave",
                "Father Ted"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "Friends.mp3",
            "category": "TV",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the TV show",
            "correct_answer": "Friends",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Will &amp; Grace",
                "Seinfeld",
                "Episodes"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "Game_of_Thrones.mp3",
            "category": "TV",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the TV show",
            "correct_answer": "Game of Thrones",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Once Upon a Time",
                "True Blood",
                "Supernatural"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "Jonathan_Creek.mp3",
            "category": "TV",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the TV show",
            "correct_answer": "Jonathan Creek",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Taggart",
                "Silent Witness",
                "Midsomer Murders"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "Lucifer.mp3",
            "category": "TV",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the TV show",
            "correct_answer": "Lucifer",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Money Heist",
                "Arrow",
                "Good Omens"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "Mastermind.mp3",
            "category": "TV",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the TV show",
            "correct_answer": "Mastermind",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Eggheads",
                "The Chase",
                "Catchphrase"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "Only_Fools_and_Horses.mp3",
            "category": "TV",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the TV show",
            "correct_answer": "Only Fools and Horses",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "One Foot in the Grave",
                "Last of the Summer Wine",
                "A Touch of Frost"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "Parks_and_Rec.mp3",
            "category": "TV",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the TV show",
            "correct_answer": "Parks and Recreation",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "30 Rock",
                "Community",
                "Modern Family"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "Peep_Show.mp3",
            "category": "TV",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the TV show",
            "correct_answer": "Peep Show",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "The Inbetweeners",
                "The Thick of It",
                "The IT Crowd"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "Poirot.mp3",
            "category": "TV",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the TV show",
            "correct_answer": "Poirot",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Inspector Morse",
                "Prime Suspect",
                "Midsomer Murders"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "Rick_and_Morty.mp3",
            "category": "TV",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the TV show",
            "correct_answer": "Rick and Morty",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Archer",
                "Final Space",
                "Futurama"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "The_Crown.mp3",
            "category": "TV",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the TV show",
            "correct_answer": "The Crown",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "The Royals",
                "The Windsors",
                "The Queen"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "The_Witcher.mp3",
            "category": "TV",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the TV show",
            "correct_answer": "The Witcher",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Arrow",
                "Xena&#58; Warrior Princess",
                "The Last Kingdom"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "Tiger_King.mp3",
            "category": "TV",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the TV show",
            "correct_answer": "Tiger King",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Making a Murderer",
                "Killer Inside&#58; The Mind of Aaron Hernandez",
                "The Confession Tapes"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "Twin_Peaks.mp3",
            "category": "TV",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the TV show",
            "correct_answer": "Twin Peaks",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "The Killing",
                "True Detective",
                "Blindspot"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "american_pyscho.mp3",
            "category": "Film",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the film",
            "correct_answer": "American Pyscho",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "The Texas Chainsaw Massacre",
                "A Nightmare on Elm Street",
                "Fight Club"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "ben_hur.mp3",
            "category": "Film",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the film",
            "correct_answer": "Ben-Hur",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "The Ten Commandments",
                "Lawrence of Arabia",
                "Spartacus"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "goldfinger.mp3",
            "category": "Film",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name this Bond film",
            "correct_answer": "Goldfinger",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Thunderball",
                "Diamonds Are Forever",
                "Live and Let Die"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "gone_with_the_wind.mp3",
            "category": "Film",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the film",
            "correct_answer": "Gone with the Wind",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Ben-Hur",
                "Casablanca",
                "Citizen Kane"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "goodfellas.mp3",
            "category": "Film",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the actor behind this famous improv",
            "correct_answer": "Joe Pesci",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Danny DeVito",
                "Tommy DeVito",
                "Steve Buscemi"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "it.mp3",
            "category": "Film",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "What is this dancing clown's name?",
            "correct_answer": "Pennywise",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "It",
                "Robert Gray",
                "Sergeant Terry Jeffords"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "john_wick.mp3",
            "category": "Film",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Who is the man they are referring to?",
            "correct_answer": "John Wick",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Keanu Reeves",
                "Neo",
                "Mr. Anderson"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "knives_out.mp3",
            "category": "Film",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the film",
            "correct_answer": "Knives Out",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Clue",
                "Uncut Gems",
                "The Gentlemen"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "nightcrawler.mp3",
            "category": "Film",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the actor playing the interviewer",
            "correct_answer": "Jake Gyllenhaal",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Riz Ahmed",
                "Jake Gyllenhall",
                "Jake Gillenhall"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "pulp_fiction.mp3",
            "category": "Film",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Where did they get the burger from?",
            "correct_answer": "Big Kahuna",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Burger King",
                "McDonalds",
                "Los Pollos Hermanos"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "scarface.mp3",
            "category": "Film",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Which actor features in this clip?",
            "correct_answer": "Steven Bauer",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Al Pachino",
                "Mark Margolis",
                "Robert Loggia"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "silence_of_the_lambs.mp3",
            "category": "Film",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the film",
            "correct_answer": "Silence of the Lambs",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Manhunter",
                "Hannibal",
                "Red Dragon"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "snow_white.mp3",
            "category": "Film",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the film",
            "correct_answer": "Snow White",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Fantasia",
                "Cinderella",
                "Dumbo"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "talladega_nights.mp3",
            "category": "Film",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Name the film",
            "correct_answer": "Talladega Nights",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Step Brothers",
                "The Other Guys",
                "Blades of Glory"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "the_big_lebowski.mp3",
            "category": "Film",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Who plays The Dude in this film?",
            "correct_answer": "Jeff Bridges",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "John Goodman",
                "Steve Buscemi",
                "John Turturro"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "the_big_short.mp3",
            "category": "Film",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Who is the real person that Steve Carell is representing?",
            "correct_answer": "Steve Eisman",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Mark Baum",
                "Michael Burry",
                "Jarred Vannett"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "the_matrix.mp3",
            "category": "Film",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Who is demanding a phone call?",
            "correct_answer": "Mr. Anderson",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Mr. Harrison",
                "Mr. Walker",
                "Mr. Emerson"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "hasta_la_vista.mp3",
            "category": "Film",
            "specialism": "Arnie",
            "type": "multiple",
            "question": "Which film did the catchphrase &quot;Hasta la Vista&quot; originate from?",
            "correct_answer": "Terminator 2: Judgment Day",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Terminator",
                "Terminator 3: Rise of the Machines",
                "Terminator Genisys"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "ill_be_back.mp3",
            "category": "Film",
            "specialism": "Arnie",
            "type": "multiple",
            "question": "Which film did the catchphrase &quot;I'll be back&quot; originate from?",
            "correct_answer": "Terminator",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Terminator 2: Judgment Day",
                "Terminator 3: Rise of the Machines",
                "Terminator Genisys"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "commando.mp3",
            "category": "Film",
            "specialism": "Arnie",
            "type": "multiple",
            "question": "Which film did Arnie kill Sully?",
            "correct_answer": "Commando",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True Lies",
                "Eraser",
                "End of Days"
            ]
        },
        {
            "meta": "Audio",
            "metaSrc": "commando.mp3",
            "category": "Film",
            "specialism": "Arnie",
            "type": "multiple",
            "question": "Which film did Arnie kill Sully?",
            "correct_answer": "Commando",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True Lies",
                "Eraser",
                "End of Days"
            ]
        }
    ]
}